http://www.calweb.com/policies/privacy-statement

HomeSitemapEmail VerifyOur ServicesCalWeb Fiber, Broadband, and DSLWordPress Customer CareDomain Name RegistrationJoomla Web DesignBusinessWeb HostingWeb Hosting Order FormManage Your DomainMass email managerSupportMy AccountBillingWebmail LoginMailGuard Loginmore....PoliciesPrivacy StatementAcceptable UseTerms and ConditionsContact Us
Privacy StatementCalWeb Internet Services has a firm commitment to privacy. We take your privacy concerns seriously and want to make every effort to address them. That is why we have adopted the following policy, which explains our position on information-gathering and disclosure.
Your Personal Information
From time to time, we will ask for information that personally identifies you, as in our user surveys or registration for CalWeb Internet Services services such as e-mail, forums, or promotions. We use this information to operate CalWeb Internet Services's services, provide you with the highest quality services and offer you opportunities we think will be of interest.
We will not disclose any personal information without your advance permission except when we believe the law requires us to do so or the disclosure is necessary to protect the rights or property of CalWeb Internet Services, or as explained below or in our Terms and Conditions.
In order to describe our services to prospective partners, advertisers and others, we may disclose user information but only in a form that does not identify individual users. For example, we might disclose that a certain percentage of our users are male or within a certain age range.
Occasionally, we may disclose personal information in other circumstances, but we will only do this if we have explained at the time we collect the information the purpose for which it will be disclosed.
Kids' Privacy
CalWeb Internet Services is particularly concerned with providing a safe online environment for kids. Therefore, in areas operated by CalWeb Internet Services that are directed to kids or when we learn that a user is under the age of 13, we will ask for parental consent before collecting additional personal information about the child or allowing the child to use the CalWeb Internet Services services to provide additional personal information. Parental consent can be provided by Sending a fax copy of a completed Terms and Conditions, including your signature, to the facsimile number provided on the Minor Disclaimer Section.
CalWeb Internet Services will not knowingly disclose personal information about users under the age of 13 without prior parental consent, except as required by law. If for any reason you wish to access, update or remove information about your child or terminate your child's account, you may fax or call CalWeb Internet Services at the numbers listed in our contact us section or send an e-mail.
CalWeb Internet Services strongly recommends parental supervision when a child uses the Internet, and particularly when a child enters a forum or uses e-mail. We also encourage parents to instruct their children not to give out personal information in these areas.
E-Commerce
CalWeb Internet Services hosts a number of online stores that sell a variety of goods and services. These stores may collect information from you such as your name, credit card number and other contact information. CalWeb Internet Services does not
collect, use or disclose this information nor does it own or control the stores or have responsibility for transactions made by those merchants. If you would like to know more about the information collected when you participate in e-commerce on or through this site, please contact the store merchants directly.
Cookies
A "cookie" is a small data text file that is placed in your browser and allows CalWeb Internet Services to recognize you each time you visit this site. Cookies themselves do not contain any personal information, and CalWeb Internet Services does not use cookies to collect personal information. Instead, they allow us to see which parts of our site you have used so that we can better serve you when you return to our site. Cookies may be used to provide you with information and special opportunities tailored to your interests.
Direct Mailings and "Opting Out"
We may send you information about various products and services. If you don't want to receive this information, you can "opt out" by sending us an e-mail and requesting that you not receive any of these of these offers.
You Can Change Your Private Information at any Time
Information you provide to CalWeb Internet Services may be stored by us for an indefinite time. However, please feel free to change, update or delete this information at any time by sending an e-mail or call our offices at 916-641-9320.
Remember the Risks Whenever You Use the Internet
You should know that when you voluntarily disclose personal information on the CalWeb Internet Services system (for example, in forums), that information can be collected and used by others and may result in unsolicited messages from other people. While we do our best to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of any information that you transmit to CalWeb Internet Services and you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of any passwords or other account information. In addition, our partners and other Internet sites or services that may be accessible through CalWeb Internet Services have separate data and privacy practices independent of us, and therefore we disclaim any responsibility or liability for their policies
or actions. Please contact those vendors and others directly if you have any questions about their privacy policies.
If you have any questions or comments about our policies, please e-mail us or call our offices at 916-641-9320.
Designed by CalWeb Internet Services, Inc..
